This is a corpus of texts collected from the internet. See more information at http://www.corpora.heliohost.org/.
See statistics for the corpus at http://www.corpora.heliohost.org/statistics.html.

For further info: hc.corpus@gmail.com

Conditions of use:

The HC Corpora contain text from publicly accessible sources. All data have been processed automatically so that it is not possible to reconstruct the original source texts. 
The HC corpora are not protected by copyright. They may be used for any purpose, excluding commercial use without prior consent. If you make use of any of the corpora all I ask is that you put a reference to my web page and my e-mail somewhere in your work.

Disclaimer:

The HC Corpora have been processed automatically from publicly accessible sources based on the outlined methodology without considering in detail the content of the contained text. No responsibility is taken for the content of the data. In particular, the views and opinions expressed in specific parts of the data remain exclusively with the authors.